{"data":[{"question":"Philip is a child prodigy. He graduated from college _____ the age of eleven.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At the age of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"I thought we were going to be late, but we arrived at the concert _____ time.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"-On time = at the planned time; neither late nor early\n-In time = with enough time to spare; before the last moment","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Let's talk that over _____ lunch.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"\"Call me,\" said the doctor, \"if you develop a fever _____ the next few days.\"","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"What are you doing _____ New Year's Eve?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"_____ the beginning of the 20th century, the United States was still a predominantly agricultural society.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n- At the beginning of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Rock and roll began _____ the fifties.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"We usually visit our relatives in Vermont _____ Christmas.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Patricia doesn't usually go out _____ night.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Some people say the ghost appears in the castle _____ the stroke of midnight.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"}]}